shopsocially.com 2019-06-01

# ShopSocially Customer Loyalty Program | Referral Marketing | Privacy Policy

ShopSocially is a service offered by Velocita, Inc. d/b/a ShopSocially (“ShopSocially”), a California Corporation located at 339 N. Bernardo Avenue, Mountain View, CA 94043. This privacy policy applies to individual users who use ShopSocially or its related services to share data across social channels.

This Privacy Policy describes ShopSocially’s policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. ShopSocially receives your information through its website at http://shopsocially.com (the “ _Website_ “), APIs, customer integrations and third-parties (collectively known as the “ _Service_ “). When using our Service you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by ShopSocially in the United States or any other country where ShopSocially operates. If you reside outside the U.S. your personally identifiable information may be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Service and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the US.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [privacy@shopsocially.com](mailto:privacy@shopsocially.com).

## **Information Collection and Use**

Our primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the product and Service made available through the Service, including, but not limited, to the Service, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.

### **Information Collected Upon Registration.**

If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Service, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to ShopSocially. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service, or share a purchase from a partner retailer  via Facebook or if you desire to receive marketing materials and information. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, and other information that you decide to provide us with, or that you decide to include in your public profile.

### **Additional Information**

Your full user name and your photo, if you have uploaded one on Facebook, are displayed to people in the ShopSocially network, general public and to people visiting third-party sites where ShopSocially is installed. Once a member, you may provide additional information in the profile section. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself in the ShopSocially system.

ShopSocially may collect purchase data such as product URL, product title, product price, product currency, product category and product id as well as personally identifiable data such as your name, facebook profile, date of birth, email address, postal code, mailing address, birthday, friend list, interest list and other personal information from our retailer partners when you share a purchase via ShopSocially. ShopSocially will own rights to this data and ShopSocially may use this data to provide additional services to you or to other users. ShopSocially may share this data with the retailer partners to provide an enhanced shopping experience on their website. For example, your name, profile photo, facebook URL, your shared purchase product info and user comment may be displayed in a shopping community view on the retailer partner’s Facebook page or website. This info may also be displayed when another user visits the page of a product that you have previously shared.

If you contact us by email through the Service, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.

### **Use of Contact Information**

In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information including but not limited to our Service. We do not spam our members. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please email [privacy@shopsocially.com](mailto:privacy@shopsocially.com).

### **Log Data**

When you visit the Service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data” ). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any links on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Service and of our Service, and for the Service’s technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service.

## **Cookies**

Like many websites, we also use “cookie” technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Service and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. ShopSocially may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Service and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Service, and to improve the Service. A session cookie enables certain features of the Service and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Service. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

## **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

### **Service Providers**

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide Service to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such Service, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

### **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

ShopSocially cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of ShopSocially or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

### **Business Transfers**

ShopSocially may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## **Changing or Deleting Information**

If you are a registered user of the Service, you may access and update or correct the information you provided to us by e-mailing us at [privacy@shopsocially.com](mailto:privacy@shopsocially.com).

## **Security**

ShopSocially is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Service in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

## **Links to Other Websites**

Our Service contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other Services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

## **Our Policy Towards Children**

The Service is not directed to persons under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@shopsocially.com.](mailto:privacy@shopsocially.com) We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.

**Last updated:**  April 1, 2015

ShopSocially (Velocita, Inc.)  
5201 Great America Parkway, Suite 351, Santa Clara, CA 95054
